Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching
Merry Christmas!
As Christmas is coming up in 20 days
This time, we have a special version!
This is a special version!
Black Santa and Red Santa!
Yay!
Merry Christmas!
They've accepted me.
But you're right... it's too soon.
Really?
He went right into it.
It's in 20 days.
That's right.
Almost there!
Almost there. 20 days.
And now...
Merry Cree.
I'm proud of you.
Good evening.
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
The morning chimes have rung.
We are Shiri and I am the MC of the show.
Before we begin, we'd like to choose today's MC.
Please vote for one or two, whichever you prefer.
This way.
The person who has the number card with the number on it is the MC.The person with the number tag with that number on it is the MC.
Yes, okay.
Let's start voting.
Here we go.
Invisible.
Invisible, invisible?
Shuffle it around.
Okay, here you go.
Here you go.
I got it.
Which one's more?
Which is more?
Jingle dangle.
That's what I mean.
It rang.
It rang a little bit.
Can I go now?
It's not happening at the most important time.
Why not?
Let's try this.
Ding, dong, dong.
Okay, we're done.
So, which was more?
There were more 2s.
You want to see?
So...
Let's see!
So, Cocona, who has the number 2 card, will be today's MC.
Please give her my best regards.I look forward to working with you.
You're fresh.
Yes, that's why I'll be your MC today.
My name is Cocona Sakurai.
Pleased to meet you.
Thank you very much.
Yes, so I would like to start right away.
Ebichu's
The Comfortable and Fufufuna Showroom
Yes, thank you very much for watching the 64th Annual EBITCHU's Funny and Fufufu Showroom today.
Ebichu's Expanding and Fufufuna Showroom is the sister show of our sister show, Ukka-san's showroom.
Yes, so it's spreading time here!
In order to get as many people as possible to watch this distribution, we are going to make an announcement on the official X of Ebichu now, so please spread the word everyone.
Please spread the word.
Is there a Christmas-like bug?
Triangle is fixed.
I'll take four pictures.
They say it's a Christmas-like pose.
What's this?
A tree.
That's what it is.
It's a tree.
I have an announcement from the showroom,
The showroom recently celebrated its 10th anniversary.
Congratulations!
Mr. Nakayama, do you have any memories of this showroom?
The showroom has grown to 10 people, and now there are about 2 people in the showroom each, and we deliver once a month,
When was the last time I was here?
It's been a long time indeed.It has indeed been a very long time.
It's been a long time.
It's been four, hasn't it?
It's been a long time for me, too. Did I come this year?
Did I come?
Is it at that level?
Summer? Oh, no.
But I did it with someone.
I didn't do it alone.
I'm sure you feel like you did it with someone else because you didn't do it alone,
I did it with someone,
But I feel like I did it with my sisters.
Are you sure?
Yes, I did.
February!
No, just this year.
Just this year.
February.
But it's already winter.
Winter?
July!
Is it? Recently?
July?
Is it winter only? I can only come here in winter.
You mean you're a winter girl?
Yes, yes, yes. I can't come in the summer.
I can't come in the summer.
Next year, then.
Then next summer.Then next year, summer.
See you in winter.
Winter, winter, right?
See you in about 4,000 yen.
Indeed.
But I'm happy to be able to deliver today.
I'm happy.
Yes, so, you know, we already have a limited ambassador for the 10th anniversary at SHOWROOM ....
Oh, I can't say.
You're going to ring me as an ambassador?
EBITCHU?
Is that OK?
No, you can't. Stop now.
The implementation of limited ambassadors and gifts...
Implementation?
Implementation.
They're having special 10th anniversary events, etc., and they also had a giveaway on Ebitu's SHOWROOM.
Yes.
First of all, I would like to give away the 10th anniversary T-shirts, which are the 10th anniversary goods of SHOWROOM, with autographs of Hoshina & Kobayashi, who appeared in the last show....
Signs...
I understand if you want to put "San" on Hoshina and Kobayashi, but I don't want "San" on their signatures.
When I read it up to Kobayashi, I thought it was a throwaway, so now I put a "san" on the poser.
Mr. Sign and our two signers.
And also the name of the winner.
Yes.
We were planning to give away one of them, but thank you very much for all the entries.
Thank you very much.
What do you think? What do you think of this T-shirt?
T-shirt? It's great. The winner's name is already written on it, so it's a spoiler.
It's quite a spoiler.Quite a bit, spoiler alert.
For this next one.
Yes, I know. So, finally, I would like to announce the winner.
I'd like to announce it.
The winner is Ho-chan Eka.
Congratulations.
Yes, I am. We will send a DM to Ms. Ho-chan Eka via the official SHOWROOM X.
Yes.
This is the announcement from SHOWROOM. Congratulations!
Congratulations!
Amazing.
Yes.
Hey.
Hey, you're goofing off.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's still okay.
Okay. So, today, we're going to go to this project.
Okay.
The title is.
Yes.
Survey talk.
Yay.
Yes. A questionnaire talk is a talk in which the participants are asked to fill out a questionnaire before the talk to determine the content of the talk.
Yes.
Yes. Well, let's get started, shall we?
Okay.
I will announce the theme of the talk.
We've done this before, haven't we?You did something like this before.
Yes.
1. The story of Sin-Asha.
Yes. 2.
2. EBICHU's buzzword of the year award.
Yes. 3.
3). What you want to do this year.
Yes.
④. Let's think about this year's Kanji.
5). Riko Nakayama's second photo book.
Oh.
⑥. Sakuragi Cocona's first photo book will be released.
Yeah.
And ⑦ is what I want to talk about. So, what do you do in a situation like this?
Oh, I'm curious.
And ⑧ is Cocona. I've noticed the deliciousness of the ____ that Cocona wants to talk about.
I'm sorry.
And ⑩is two people, looking for a travel destination for Cocorico.
It is.
I'm going to ask you this.
We are now accepting votes on which talk theme you would like to hear, so please throw out the one you are interested in. Please throw in your favorite one.
Please vote for your favorites.
Please start.
I would like to talk a lot about the first-ranked topic.
This is the latest one, so I feel like I want to talk about it the most.
I want to talk about this one. This is today.
Oh, sorry. Oh, sorry. It's a bit much.
I left today.It came out today.
Because today.
That's right.
That's right. I'd like to hear that, wouldn't you?
I'd like to hear that, wouldn't you, guys?
One, one, one.
Okay, well, I guess it's time to go.
Ding-dong.
Which one?
Done.
So everyone's a 1.
I'll tell you a story.
Today, around noon?
It's out.
Sriracha has been announced.
Did it come out? Just now.
Oh, here it is.
Beautiful blue.
It was a beautiful sunny day, not a cloud in the sky.
It was really hot.
But that's why it was so beautiful, but everyone looked a little dazzled.
But, you know, this was not facing the direction of the sun.
It was fine at this time, wasn't it?
We shot it on a tennis court, and the outfit, too, Thread.
She's a sporty girl, isn't she?
Cute.
Super cute.
Everyone was cute that day.
Also on this day?On this day, too?
Usually?
They are always cute,
But these beautiful women are all very nice, aren't they?
Everyone has their own style.
Yes, Nonoka has been doing this hairstyle lately.
She wears her bangs in a braid. Is this a recent trend?
It's quite popular in the K-pop world,
It looks good on Nonohana.
It looks good on her.
Braiding hair in the front is quite popular.
There are many unusual hairstyles.
Nonoka Hatsukado.
Ms. Nakayama.
She has her hair in the center.
I've decided.
This is in order of attendance number, right?
That's right.
Well, isn't it usually in order of attendance number?
That's true.
I see.
Summer Greeters are also in order of attendance number.
So that's how it is.
That's true.
Yuna-chan is showing her deco.
It's true.
There you are. You are here.
You are here, aren't you?
They have decoctions.
They are all beautifully white.
Moreover, Kaho, who was sitting there, and I and Cocona, we were so close to the reflector.
That's right.
Cocona and Kahochan are especially too white, so they are very white.
They were so white and beautiful.
I was really happy.
It was a really nice day.
There were no clouds.
Right.
Yeah.
I have a lot to say, but I'm going to say it.
I'm afraid I'm going to slip.
I'm scared. Shall I leave it at that?
I'll leave it at that.
Please look forward to the individual personals.
Oh, you know.
I think everyone might look more dazzled in the individual show.
Oh no, that's right. The individual partials were really bad.
They all look amazing.
But they're cute, so don't worry.
Yes, they are cute.
Enjoy.
Okay, shall we continue?
Yes, let's continue.
Please vote with everyone you notice and care about.Please vote with everyone you notice and care about.
Please do.
Start.
Pon.
It's done.
Pon. Pon.
Two too many.
Valid word general.
Mmmmmmmmmmmmmm.
Of course it's cute.
It's obvious.
Of course. Can I go now?
Yes.
Purple.
Well, who had more?
One?
Two of the next two. Number two.
That means 7?
Me? 7?
Is it 7, or is it not 1, or is it 7?
I couldn't read the number. It's a 7.
It's a seven.
What do you do in a case like this? I'm curious. What is it?
Today, I ate pasta by myself before the SHOWROOM broadcast.
I like spicy pasta, so I put a lot of Tabasco on it.
You eat pasta alone, pour a lot of Tabasco on it, and when you eat it, it's so sour that you get an "ugh" feeling.
Yes, I do. What would you do if you were alone?
What? What? What? What? What? What?
Oh, my God! Oh, my God.
Just do it.
What would you do in that situation?
Wait a minute.
If it were a friend, there would be someone to laugh at you.
How would you cover it up by yourself?
I'll cover it up.
What do you do in a situation like this?
Sure, I do. But I'm the type of person who says it all out loud.
I say it all out loud. Like, "This is spicy.
Even when you are alone?
I say it out loud. I totally say it out loud.
But I don't think I'm weird for saying it.
That's true.
I tell myself what's on my mind, like, "This is hard for me.
What do you often do alone?
I love eating alone. I also like to eat alone.
He seems to enjoy it.
When it tastes good, I say "yummy" a lot.
He mumbles to himself. I think that's the beauty of eating alone.
Is that so?
Including your impressions. I don't really care.
There are times when you feel awkward.
What do you do?
What do you do? How did you get over it? How did you get over it?
Nothing happened. It was just the way it was.
I had a sense of comfort.
I had friends around me, and I was blotting it out on my own.
I wondered what I should do. What am I supposed to do?
What would be the best way for me to do it?
Do you have one? First way, please.
What is it?
I don't care. Just say nothing and drink the water.
Cough it up.
Oh.
Are you leaving? I'm leaving even if I'm eating.
I'm leaving.
Don't leave.
I might make a sound. I'll pretend nothing's wrong.
Cough to cover it up. I'll put on a nonchalant face.
I don't care. Oh, I see.
Smirk.
I'll try this kind of smirk.
I can smirk. Maybe I should smirk too.
I wonder if it's bad that YUKAN is alone in his thoughts.
But isn't it cute that he says it's delicious? Even though he's alone.
She said it's delicious. Isn't it cute?
I think it's cute.
The last time I went to eat raw oysters alone, I said they were beautiful the moment they arrived.
They are beautiful.
When I was a little attracted to the waitress.
I could understand if his impression was, "They are beautiful. I could understand if he said it looked delicious.
It's beautiful.
Everyone is acting like they can afford it. I'll make room. Thank you very much.
I solved it. Thank you very much.
What would you like to hear next? What would you like to hear?
Let's start the voting!
We've got it right. I'm curious about this one, too, and number 8. I'm curious about this one, too. I'm curious about this one, too, and number 8.
What did you notice? What did you notice?
What did you notice?
After 13 hedges, you'll start to feel sick.
This is a proven fact.
Why does that make you feel good? Like an emo experience?
I often feel sick in my chest because I take too much zinc.
Yes.
I can take zinc.
Okay, we're done.
Okay, let's go,
Number 8!
Ah!
That's right.
What did you notice? Cocona.
Yes, I did,
I noticed the taste of albacore.
Oh, the taste of albacore.
Have you ever eaten albacore? Riko.
No, I don't remember eating it.
No, albacore are outrageous, they are.
What does it taste like?
Dangerous.
Dangerous?
Dangerous. Don't ruin my love of raw oysters. By you.
Oh, no?
No, it was that good.
Ew.
It was kind of like a little boiled ponzu when I ate it,It was kind of like a little boiled ponzu when I ate it,
It kind of melted in my mouth,
It really melted in my mouth. It was like a thick honey.
And then, there was a refreshing ponzu aroma,
It was so delicious.
It's raw and creamy.
Is it similar to latkes?
It looks like it, but it's not.
It's like, "Wow, it's really good!
That's the beauty of it.
Wow.
You're an adult. What you like, you're like an adult. Like kids.
Like albacore.
That's right. Gaki, albacore.
Yes.
Anko?
What's anko?
Anko's liver?
Oh, I've never had it.
I'm curious.
I wonder.
I wonder what bean-jam liver tastes like. I love liver, too.
Oh, liver, liver I like too.
Do you still, um, do you still have the kid?
Not at all.
Oh, do you have any?
No, I don't have any.
You don't have any?
Do you like the sea? Like things from the sea?
I like things from the sea. I've been told I'm a bean.
Oh, gout? Gout. Oh, if you eat too much of that kind of thing. That's what my grandfather said. Yes, yes, if you eat too much good food.
What is gout? Well, don't worry about it.
Don't mind it? Never mind.
Anko is said to be close to Kimoshiroko. It is more refreshing than "shi-bar.
It is true that liver has a little bit of a habit. I didn't feel it was that habitual.
I'm curious. It was very tasty. It was boiled.
Yes, they do.
Do you have it? I want to eat it. I'm more interested in the raw ones. You know, oysters can be a hit or something. Yes, there are. How about albacore? Do you get a chance to win an albacore?
You don't get a chance to win an albacore? But I think you might win if they are raw.
Or fungus. I used to like oysters, but when I eat them
I get sick to my stomach. I thought it was bad. It's not like I'm going to get sick. I thought maybe I didn't like them.
It's hard for me to eat them. Even though it's delicious. When I went on a trip to Hokkaido with Ayaka before, I ate one of them and I couldn't eat any more.
I got so sick I couldn't even stand up. Not even one? Just one.
Years later, I went to Mie Prefecture and ate oysters with Ayaka.
I knew it was no good. I thought it was no good. Whenever I go on a trip with Ayaka, I always hit it.
Oh, no. Not with Ayaka.
The albino snores a little. Oh, I see. It goes a little smooth.
Looks delicious. I want to try one. I'd like to try one that's a little tasty.
It's easy to hit the right person. I knew it. I got a note saying I'm sad.
Sad? Sad?
Yes, it was. The most delicious food of the year. What was it?
Do you have one?
I think I've had enough of albacore.
I don't know if it was the best one this year, but I bought it at a convenience store in New Zealand.
Convenience store? There you go.
The meat pie was delicious. You ate it.
The meat pie was delicious. New Zealand is famous for its meat pies.
And you can get the same quality of deliciousness at a convenience store.And that delicious quality at a convenience store.
Yes, it's amazing that they can do that.
It was amazing that they could serve it.
It was really good.
But it didn't seem that expensive.
The quality of the convenience store was super high.
It was really delicious.
I thought, "If you come to New Zealand now, you might say lamb.
I haven't eaten lamb.
You haven't eaten lamb?
I didn't eat lamb. I didn't order it.
I was with Rikachan and Reko-chan, the sisters sitting next to me.
Oh, you went to Mayireko's table.
You did order, right?
You did ask for it, didn't you?
Yes, we did.
We didn't order, so we couldn't eat.
Was it GBA?
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, I didn't know that.
I ate it and it was delicious.
You didn't get to eat it?
It was so good.
I knew it had no smell.
Oh, really?
That's the part that I thought was a little stinky.
It has a smell, doesn't it?
It was super delicious.
New Zealand is a bit similar to Japan.
Hey, hey. Hey, hey.
It was a little cheap.
It didn't feel too foreign.
Yeah.
In the comments, what did you enjoy the most this year? I'm curious. What was the best food this year?
Please tell me. It seems like everyone seems to be eating a lot of delicious food.
Transform, transform, transform. I don't know.
What did you eat?
What did you eat? What did you have?
I like salmon roe that I had in Hokkaido during the tour.
The salmon roe sushi we had for dinner was amazing!
Really?
The barbecue at Tamago Rice.
Tamago-mai?
Yakiniku at Tamago Rice!
From one of our spring tour guests.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much!
The egg rice was delicious!
Sushi is so big!
It was delicious!
Tamago Mai.
Tamago mai!
Hokkaido parfait...
What's the salted skipjack entrails? I'm super curious.
Oh, wow, wow.
It's delicious. What's salted?
I wonder if they eat it raw. I'm super curious.
Cocona seems to like that kind of entrails.Cocona seems to be a favorite, visceral type.
Hocky mussels are also delicious.
Do you like seafood? I can eat it.
The okonomiyaki we had in Hiroshima on the Hal tour.
Okonomiyaki is super delicious. It has all the goodness of Hiroshima!
I love sea urchin hollen!
Early soba in Okinawa.
Speaking of Okinawa,
The gnocchi I had at a hotel in Okinawa was delicious.
What?
Did you eat gnocchi?
I haven't.
What?
It was at the buffet.
I didn't go this morning.
You didn't go?
No, I didn't.
You should go.
Do you think we'll stay at that hotel?
Maybe next time?
That hokke... hokke? The gnocchi is that...
Hockey and gnocchi mixed together.
The gnocchi was creamy and there were sea grapes on top, the saltiness and creaminess went really well together.
Gnocchi is the best.
It was my first time to try gnocchi, but I realized it was my first time to eat gnocchi.
Gnocchi tamen
Have you ever been to the North Pole? I will eat at the North Pole.
It's amazing. I'm getting sick of spicy food. It's more of a challenge than a delicious food.
I eat it as if it is a challenge. Do you think it's spicy? I definitely think so. It's extremely spicy.
So Amirei-chan is the strongest right now?So Amirei-chan is the strongest right now?
Yuna is also strong.
I would like to see a showdown among geiko.
I hope so.
I want you to do it.
I won't do it anymore.
Yes, I've had a bad one recently.
I wonder why.
I guess I get weak when I stop eating.
I'm used to spicy food, aren't I?
That's true.
At least one more.
Okay, I'm done.
I'll go one more.
What would you like to ask?
I'd like to ask you about your photo book, since you seem to have been there recently.
As much as I can tell you.
As much as we can talk about.
There are a lot of things.
I have a lot of things.
How spicy do you want your curry at Coco Ichiba?
I only like sweet curry.
I like everything else spicy.
Curry is sweet.
I see.
Isn't Coco Ichi-e even 1 spicy?
It's kind of spicy, isn't it?
That's why I prefer sweet curry.
Let's start.Let's get started.
Start.
Yes, sir.
What's the number? Number 6?
Oh, number 6!
Coconner's first photo book is coming out!
I just got back.
I know, right? Recently, right?
Recently. I'm home.
I'm back.
I've been shooting a photo book.
Lovely?
I also thought it was very unusual for you to send out a message in a lovely way.
When you announced it, you hadn't done any shooting yet, right?
When I was going to Thailand, I announced in a timely manner that I was going there and that I had just returned,
It was a lot of fun to share the experience with everyone.
Thailand is said to be the land of smiles.
Everyone is smiling.
Really. Even if they are not smiling, if you smile, they will definitely smile back.
Wow.
That's why I found it interesting that they serve in-flight meals on airplanes.
The person who brought the in-flight meal was Thai, and he told me that the pork was chicken,
I thought, "Oh, I kind of want to eat pork," so I said, "Pork please,
I wanted pork, so I said "Pork please" and was told "NO.
Why?
Isn't it terrible?
What? Why?
She smiles so much, gets punished right in front of me, says no, and then says, "Oh, I'll have chicken then.
No? You mean there isn't any?
I know there isn't, but I was wondering why you said pork with chicken.
Certainly. You gave me a choice.
Why did you give it to me? I wondered what kind of a surprise it was, and I really thought it was a surprise. But then he did it to the person behind me.
I thought, "What kind of a surprise is this?
I said "pork" to the person behind me and he said "Why? I don't know what that means.
It's funny.
That's how the game is played.
A game in which you are being teased.
It was interesting.
They're messing with you.
It's interesting.
Yes, it was.
The smiles on their faces were so beautiful. Everyone was really friendly. Many of them were really friendly.
What was your favorite Thai dish or meal?
Wow, there was one person who knows Thailand very well, and we worked together with him, and he let us eat delicious food every day.
Wow.
He let me go there every day and recommended some good food. So, I wonder what it is. I guess it's a face cartoon.
Ah, face manga.
Face manga.
Yeah.
I was told that this seasoning is only available in Thailand. Also, they have mango rice bowls and white rice sweets.
Do you know it? That one.
The rice is sweet, too.
Sweet. The sweet rice cake with coconut milk on it is also very tasty.
Wow, I like it. But I also went to Thailand for another photo book, and I got hooked on Thai food after I got back.
Oh, that?
It was really delicious.
After I came back to Japan, I kept thinking about that Thai food. I came back to Japan from there, and I kept thinking, oh, that Thai food.
I knew it was something different. It's authentic. It's delicious.
I thought that the real place is amazing. It's amazing.
So, what kind of Cocona can we see in this photo book?
Well, she is 18 years old, and since she is going to be published by Young Jump, there are shots of her in swimsuits and such, but she is still very much an 18-year-old, or rather, she has yet to become an adult.
There are also some cute childish parts, a side of me that I don't usually show, and some student-like parts.
Oh, yes, that's right. It's in the graduation trip category.
I went on a graduation trip.
Oh, wow.
It's fun.
I think you can see me looking at it.
When was January?
January 24.
Oh, enjoy.
Enjoy it.
Phuket 2 moves.
Riko, the senior member of the photo collection, would you like to say a few words?
Yes, I do.
Let's sell a lot!
Senpai! You've already done the shoot, right? That's right.
A lot. From here on out, we'll just have to get a lot of looks. That's the key, that's for sure.
I will do my best. Please advertise a lot, too.
Please do. Maybe there will be some events, right?
Last but not least! Yes.
Now that this is here, I have no choice but to ask about one more person's photo book.
No, no, no, no, something I want to do this year. I don't feel like I've been chosen.
Yes.
Do you want to sell them by hand?
Business?
Business.Business.
Three, two, one.
Can-can-can-can.
Yes, sir.
Yes, thank you. Please tell us about Riko Nakayama's secondary photo book.
Where have you been?
I went to Malaysia.
I've been to New Zealand in Malaysia, so I don't know anymore.
Where did you shoot? I'm going to say New Zealand.
Malaysia. It's Malaysia.
I went to Malaysia.
I think it was right around the time of the spring tour.
I was shooting from the day after Hiroshima Park to the day before Hokkaido Park.
So you were super busy.
I was. I was there.
It was great to do the spring tour and the photo book.
It was amazing.
Did you do any kind of body-building?
Muscle training? I did strength training at the gym.
I started pretty early.
Arms?
It's a hot place, so I thought it would be good if I could show off my arms and stuff.
It's a hot spot.
So I worked mainly on my arms, collarbones, and other parts of my body.
Wow.
We ate meals during the spring tour, you know, when we were on the road.
Everyone ate a lot.
Everyone went to Hiroshima to eat, but it was no use. We went back to the hotel saying that we were going to start filming tomorrow, and everyone was eating delicious food in Hiroshima,
But then we went to the supermarket and bought, you know....
I went to the supermarket and bought some sashimi and some snacks.Buy some sashimi for snacks.
Tuna or something, it sounds good.
Oh, I see.
I thought it was nice.
I felt sorry for him. At that time, I had no idea. I didn't know that he had gone through such hardship.
But after the shoot, the next day was Hokkaido, so I ate a lot after the shoot.
I ate a lot after the shoot.
You ate?
Yes, cinnamon.
It's good, isn't it?
I ate a pizza.
Wow.
Next day.
The next day.
That's right, ever.
Hmm.
That's how I put up with it.
But during the filming period, I went abroad, so there are a lot of delicious foods from overseas.
So I ate them.
Yes. I had been holding back until I got there, but on the day I went, I bought a chocolate race at a convenience store and ate it.
Wait a minute, they said they were filming the next day.
Is that foreign magic?
Overseas magic.
It was overseas magic.
It can't be helped.
It can't be helped. It's no use.
It was chocolate ice cream, not some Malaysian thing.
Chocolate ice cream.
I don't understand.I don't understand.
Did you eat it?
I ate it.
It was foreign magic.
It's foreign magic. Yes, it's foreign magic and zero-calorie.
Zero calories.
It's okay.
Well, it's good, you know, it's already on the market, so mine is.
Yes, it is.
Did you guys buy it?
What do you think? Have you seen it?
Have you seen it? I mean, did you buy it?
I'm pushing hard.
What do you think? How do you like it? Be honest. You can't do it yet.
Yes, I can.
Are there any of you?
Raise your hand if you haven't bought one yet.
I didn't put it on display today.
And please buy Sakurai Coconut, too.
You can buy it, right?
Of course you can.
Please take a look at this.
If you haven't done so yet.
But many of you have already bought it.
Yes, you can order online now.
Yes.
Please do.
Please.Please.
It was.
Yes, is it good?
Yes, it is.
How is it?
Yes.
That's all for now, this was a pleasant and informative survey talk.
Yay.
Yes. And today, I would like to do a project like this.
It's called, "The Delightful and Fufufufu Shrimp Chew GPT.
Good morning, GPT.
GPT is a service in which an artificial intelligence instantly answers any question.
Yes, I know, I know, I know. But this time, I'd like to do an Ebichu GPT to compete with the chat GPT.
Everyone, please ask us any questions you have in the comments on the EBITCHU GPT.
Anyway, I'll try to answer as soon as possible.
Do you understand GPT? Do you understand?
Well, I think your...my explanation was a bit clunky. It was a little bit confusing, wasn't it? It was easy to understand.
Whenever I said something, you would respond with a quick "poof".
When I said something about Riko Nakayama, he would say something about Riko Nakayama.
What? Didn't Mr. Nakayama do the same thing the other day?
Is that so?
What? I did?
Oh, wait.
Oh, my God.
You're kidding?
Did you do it? Was it really GPT?
No, I didn't. My memory.
I didn't do it. I didn't do it.
If you didn't do it, then I didn't do it.Well, then, if Riko didn't do it, I didn't do it.
I didn't do it.
I'm not doing it.
Well, I guess we should get going.
Which way do you want to go first?
Can I say something? And Cocona answers right away.
I answer. Okay, I'll go.
I'll go first.
What do I need to do to lose weight? Yes, don't eat any more! This is the best. Don't eat? Not eating is the best.
If you could be born again, what would it be? A swan.
I would like to be as white and clean as a swan. What do you like about each other? What I like about Riko is that she is easy to talk to.
Riko is easy to talk to.
What is your favorite fashion item for winter?
Navel-baring knitwear.
But I was told by a fortune teller that I have a weak stomach and need to warm it up.
Yes, but it's only for this year, so I'd like to start wearing it next year.
Foods suitable for breakfast.
Banana & protein.
Ancient.
I wonder what love is.
I don't know.
No?
It's a GP if you don't answer properly.
Love is love.
Yes. What is the official name of the capital of Thailand?
I don't know.
So tell me.
Boom-boom-boom.
You really don't know?
Bangkok.Bangkok.
Yes.
What's the hottest fashion for winter?
Coats!
What would you like to say about the economic cycle of the cold versus the Pacific?
What is that?
Oh, my.
Oh, my goodness!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Hey, how's it going today?
I'll come by. I'm free.
What do you recommend for a Christmas present?
I don't know.
I just saw a bunch of scarves.
Scarves!
This, this, this.
Why all the talk about the economy?
What do you think will happen to the Japanese economy next year?
Well, it's going to explode.
It's going to blow up in all spheres.
Do you want to sleep?
I'm not sleepy! I'm fine!
What is Coconan Sakuragi's strategy?
What is your strategy? Winning?
How do you...
Strategy!
Do you want to fight? Me and...
What's your strategy for Coconan Sakuragi?What is the strategy for Coconan Sakuragi?
How should I put it?
Oh, is that what you mean? How can I get him to drop me?
Well, well, well... I don't know.
What is it?
Just tell him you like him.
Oh, wow.
That would be great.
How do flying fish fly?
What?
You told me.
Why are they so cute?
I always think they're cute.
Oh, that's nice.
What do you want to do when you become Riko Nakayama? I want to do a rollercoaster. You can't do that.
Yes, how do you beat the national defense humor?
Punch and pop.
Anyone can do it. Is there a Santa Claus? I think there is.
Yes, there is. What was the other cry?
Is it okay? Is it too random? I don't want this kind of idol. Please answer me.
They don't sing and dance, they stand on stage. I don't like that.
When will gas prices drop? It won't. It will only go up.
Prices are going up. What was the weather like today?
I think it was sunny. It depends on where you are.
Yes, it does. How to knock over a pumpkin. How to knock down a pumpkin.
Making rice cakes. In front of the pumpkin. Is there anyone you want to beat now?
Um, my skin. Oh, how do you catch Mire-chan?
Kneel down. How do I get the principal to like me?
Let's go for ramen together.
How do you beat Mayama-san?How to beat Mayama?
Win with soccer.
The end.
It was like a half comedy.
It was fun.
Funny.
It's good.
You guys get questions a lot too.
Thank you very much.
That's all for the delightful and huffing and puffing Evie Chung GPT.
Yay!
The 64th edition of the fun and fufufu showroom of Evichu has come to an end in a blink of an eye.
I would like to make an announcement here.
Announcement.
It starts here.
From here?
Yes, please.
Please do.
Since you wrote it.
Please.
Sweets Evistuak New Year University Night Club 2024 High Flying Dragons and Beyond Us will be held at Gear Arena MM on January 6 and 7, 2024.
Tickets are now on sale to the general public, so now is the time for everyone to come.
We are waiting for you.
And........,
That's all.
Yes, the fan club only event, the Ebichu members' reception will be held on February 23, 2024 at the Pacifico Yokohama National Great Hall in Yokohama, Japan, open for 4 hours.
I am looking forward to it. It will be the first time for us younger members to attend.
That's right.Yes, that's right.
Look forward to it.
One performance, anemen and motmen.
Yes, that's right. I thought about it.
Yes, there will be a reception book, so look forward to it.
And,
Sakurai Cocona first photo book will be released on January 24.
Yay.
The title is still undecided, but please look forward to it. The title is almost decided.
I see.
I'm looking forward to it.
Yes, it is.
Please look forward to it.
I'm counting on you. And I didn't write it down, but Riko Nakayama's second situation.
I really forgot to write it.
So,
Cocona, you know,
It's blank, isn't it?
Cocona said, Riko wrote it, too.
She asked me if I wanted to write.
She asked me if I wanted to write, and I said, "Thank you, Kakugaku,
What happened?
It had already started.
Yes, Riko Nakayama's second photo book was released on October 27.
I went to Malaysia and it's already on sale.
You can see it right away.
It's already on sale, so you can see it all the time. Please do.
That's right. You can see it when you buy it.
It's already on sale, so anytime. Please do.
Yes, please. Please, everyone, please take all of them.Hai. Please, all of you, by all means, please do all of this.
Please.
All of them.
All of them, please.
Okay, now I would like to announce the final top 5 ranking.
Hoi.
Yes.
Hoy! Hoy! No. 5, Mr. People. Mr. Piffle?
Mr. Piffle! Thank you! Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Fourth place, Itaya! Thank you very much!
Third place, Nappo! Thank you!
Second place, Po-chan Aga! Thank you!
1st place, Riku! Thank you!
Thank you very much!
Yes, I'm sure you will be happy with the results. So here we are. Okay? Gentlemen.
Do you have any last words?
This is the last time this year...
Last delivery.
Last showroom.
I see.
This is the last one.
One word at a time.
Thank you very much for your monthly showroom this year.
Thank you very much.
Next time I come back will be next winter.
What makes you say that?
I hope to come in January or February, but I don't know.
Maybe in November or December,
Please wait with your head held high until then. Please wait with your head held high until then.Until then, please wait with your heads held high. Please.
I beg you.
It's been a long time since I've been here,
I will be ready for spring, summer, fall, and winter.
I'm having a lot of fun in the showroom,
It's fun, isn't it?
I love summer, so I'll be waiting for you.
I love summer, so please look forward to it.
In summer.
It's fun. I love planning and stuff like that.
Please keep up the good work.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Yes, I will.
Have a happy New Year.
Merry Christmas.
Oh, wait. I didn't read this part.
That brings us to the end of the 64th edition of Ebichu's Delightful and Fufufu Showroom.
I will let you know about the next distribution as soon as I get up to it.
That's all for now, this is Shinchi Ebituac.
Merry Christmas.
One good New Year's Eve.
Thank you for watching.